function loadQuestions() {

    questionArray = [{
            question: "What is the name of the coffee shop the friends hang out at?",
            answerArray: ["Central Perk", "Starbucks", "Central Joe's", "Coffee Corner"],
            answer: "Central Perk"
        },
        {
            question: "What was the name of Pheobe's hit single?",
            answerArray: ["Pervert Parade", "Smelly Cat", "Sticky Shoes", "Lather, Rinse, Repeat"],
            answer: "Smelly Cat"
        },
        {
            question: "To get over Richard, what did Monica start making?",
            answerArray: ["Marmalade", "Jam", "Candy","Pancakes"],
            answer: "Jam"
        },
        {
            question: "What was the name of the self help book that the girls loved?",
            answerArray: ["Be Your Own Person", "Be Your Own Cleansing Pool", "Be Your Own Lightning Bearer", "Be Your Own Windkeeper"],
            answer: "Be Your Own Windkeeper"
        },
        {
            question: "What repossessed item of Joey's did Ross help pay for?",
            answerArray: ["Dog Statue", "Translucent Bird", "Jaguar Coffee Table ", "Table-top Waterfall"],
            answer: "Dog Statue"
        },
        {
            question: "What was the name of Joey and Chandler's chick?",
            answerArray: ["Chick", "Janice", "Yasmin", "Pamela"],
            answer: "Yasmin"
        },
        {
            question: "What did Ross give Phoebe, because she never had one when she was little?",
            answerArray: ["A dog", "A bike", "A dollhouse","A wagon"],
            answer: "A bike"
        },
        {
            question: "What was the name of Rachel's ex-fiance?",
            answerArray: ["Tag", "Paolo", "Barry", "Joshua"],
            answer: "Barry"
        },
        {
            question: "Who is Erica?",
            answerArray: ["Joey's Stalker", "Chandler and Monica's surrogate mother", "Ross and Rachel's daughter", "Pheobe's sister"],
            answer: "Joey's Stalker"
        },
        {
            question: "Rachel kissed a character played by which actress?",
            answerArray: ["Reece Witherspoon", "Alicia Silverstone", "Christina Applegate", "Winona Ryder"],
            answer: "Winona Ryder"
        },
        {
            question: "Charlie Sheen appeared as one of Phoebe's boyfriends. What did he do for a living?",
            answerArray: ["Teacher", "Scientist", "Naval Officer", "Firefighter"],
            answer: "Naval Officer"
        },
        {
            question: "Where does Phoebe's Scientist boyfriend, David, relocate to for work?",
            answerArray: ["Minsk", "Olso", "Stockholm", "Moscow"],
            answer: "Minsk"
        },
        {
            question: "What does Rachel's sister Amy decide to do as a career?",
            answerArray: ["Model", "Personal Shopper", "Baby Stylist", "Designer"],
            answer: "Baby Stylist"
        },
        {
            question: "What is Ross' son's name?",
            answerArray: ["Tyler", "Cole", "Dylan", "Ben"],
            answer: "Ben"
        },
        {
            question: "Joey buys one book from an encyclopedia set. Which letter does he buy?",
            answerArray: ["V", "Z", "K", "J"],
            answer: "V"
        },
        {
            question: "What card did Joey think was stolen by the guy who robbed the apartment?",
            answerArray: ["Queen of Hearts", "Ace of Spades", "Five of Spades", "Two of Clubs"],
            answer: "Five of Spades"
        },
        {
            question: "Finish the lyric: 'Home is never far away...'",
            answerArray: ["'...Home is Home Star stew'", "'...Home is in clear view'", "'...Home is Home Star brew'", "'...Home is Home Star chew'"],
            answer: "'...Home is Home Star stew'"
        },
        {
            question: "Which pairing never kissed on the show?",
            answerArray: ["Ross and Joey", "Monica and Joey", "Rachel and Chandler", "Monica and Phoebe"],
            answer: "Monica and Phoebe"
        },
        {
            question: "What did Joey name his barcalounger?",
            answerArray: ["Rosa", "Rosita", "Rosanna", "Roxanne"],
            answer: "Rosita"
        },
        {
            question: "What is Chandler's middle name?",
            answerArray: ["Marcel", "Michael", "Muriel", "Maury"],
            answer: "Muriel"
        },
    ];
};